wdrake.com 2019-05-16

# Help & Frequently Asked Questions

### Ordering Online

Click on the question below to expand the answer

You cannot cancel your submitted order through our website at this time. Please contact our Customer Service Department.

Phone: 1-855-202-7393  
Monday - Friday 8:00AM – 10:00PM  
Saturday 8:00AM – 5:00PM  
Sunday 8:00AM – 5:00PM (Central)

Email: [help@wdrake.com](mailto:help@wdrake.com)  
Please allow 24 hours in turn-around time for an email response.

Yes! Please contact our Sales Department.

**Phone: 1-855-202-7393**  
Monday-Friday 8:00AM - 10:00PM  
Saturday 8:00AM - 5:00PM  
Sunday 8:00AM – 5:00PM (Central)

**Email:  **[ **help@wdrake.com**](mailto:help@wdrake.com)  
Please allow 24 hours in turn-around time for an email response.

We do not offer that kind of payment option. However, you may download a [printable order form](https://wd.ssb-media.com/images/docs/wd_orderform.pdf) from the website and mail it in with a check.

Sales and use taxes are imposed by state and local jurisdictions on goods purchased at retail by consumers.  Retailers subject to state law are required to collect the state’s sales and use taxes from their customers.  Walter Drake collects the applicable sales tax on all orders shipped to Wisconsin.  As a result of a recent US Supreme Court decision, we are now required to collect sales and use taxes in many other states.  Each state and local jurisdiction has its own rules for what are “taxable goods” and what are exempt goods.  For states imposing sales or use taxes, your purchase is subject to use tax unless it is specifically exempt from taxation. **_Your purchase is not exempt merely because it is made over the Internet, by catalog or by other remote means._** Many states require purchasers to file a use tax return at the end of the year reporting all of the taxable purchases that were not taxed by a retailer, and to pay tax on those purchases.

Effective January 1, 2019, we will collect for AL, CO, CT, GA, HI, IL, IN, IA, KY, LA, MD, ME, MA, MI, MN, MS, NE, NV, NJ, NC, ND, OK, PA, RI, SD, UT, VT, WA, WV, WI and DC.  We will start collecting sales tax effective February 1, 2019 for SC and WY and effective April 1, 2019 for CA.  We will update this disclosure as new states enact sales and use tax collection laws. 

**_For mail orders:_**   To ensure that your order is processed, you must add sales tax for the address to which the order will be shipped. Please see <https://www.vertexinc.com/resources/tax-rate-calculator> to look-up the correct rate.

**_If you live in Puerto Rico_** , please read this information about sales and use tax.  The Commonwealth of Puerto Rico requires Puerto Rico purchasers to report all purchases that were not taxed and pay tax on those purchases.  Sales and use taxes may be reported and paid by filing Form SC 2970A, Declaration of Use of Imported Goods and Services, and pay the corresponding tax.  Individuals must file the declaration with the payment through the electronic system known as Unified Internal Revenue System (SURI).  Circular Letter 17-08 issued by the Puerto Rico Treasury Department provides further information and instructions. 

Due to our already low prices, Clearance products are not eligible for additional discounts at the order level. A Clearance item can be recognized by its sale price, which will always end in a “2”.

No, but you may register to start an online account with your own unique password during the checkout process. You may use this password to check the status of your order. You may feel free to create an online account by clicking this link: [My Account](https://www.wdrake.com/link/3f111b4d144f43a7b8319322ac60403d.aspx "My Account"). Please keep in mind that you will not be able to check your order history or the status of your order if you are not logged into your account at the time you submit an order. 

You may check the status of your order online, provided you have previously created an account. To check on the status of your order, log into your account and click on the ‘My Orders’ link. 

You can check the status of your order at any time by logging into your account and clicking on the ‘View all orders’ link. 

You can check your order history at any time by logging into your account and clicking on the ‘View all orders’ link. 

Shortly after placing your order, you will receive two separate confirmation emails. The initial confirmation does not contain any details, but lets you know we have received your order. You will then receive a more detailed confirmation within minutes of the initial confirmation email. We will also email a shipping confirmation when your order has been shipped from our fulfillment center. 

Your credit card is charged when the merchandise ships from our fulfillment center. Backorders are not charged until the merchandise ships. Once your credit card has been charged, the transaction will appear on your credit card statement as ‘w/WDR WALTER DRAKE 800-858-4979’.

We accept Visa, MasterCard, American Express, and Discover. 

**Last Updated: July 11, 2018**

These Terms of Use (“ **Terms** ”) govern your access to and use of this website (including all contents and related materials, “ **Site** ”), made available to you by Silver Star Brands, Inc., doing business as Walter Drake (“ **Company** ,” “ **we** ,” “ **us** ,” or “ **our** ”).

**By accessing or using the Site,  you (“you”) agree that you have read, understand, and agree to these Terms and our [Privacy Policy](https://www.wdrake.com/link/ecb9a7bd31cf47a69928939f14ceba53.aspx?category=8).If you do not agree with these Terms or our [Privacy Policy](https://www.wdrake.com/link/ecb9a7bd31cf47a69928939f14ceba53.aspx?category=8), please do not access or use the Site.  We recommend that you print out a copy of these Terms for your records. **

We reserve the right to modify these Terms at any time. All changes will be effective immediately upon posting to the Site and, by accessing or using the Site after changes are posted, you agree to those changes.  We will notify you of any changes by updating the “Last Updated” date at the top of this webpage. 

**Please note that these Terms contain provisions that govern the resolution of claims between Walter Drake and you.   Please see Section 18 for complete details. **

**1.  ** **Privacy Policy.  **We may collect certain information from your use of the Site as described in our [Privacy Policy](https://www.wdrake.com/link/ecb9a7bd31cf47a69928939f14ceba53.aspx?category=8), which is incorporated into these Terms and describes our information collection, use, and sharing practices.

**2.  ** **Intellectual Property Rights.  **The Site, including its text, audio, video, graphics, charts, photographs, interfaces, icons, software, computer code, data, trademarks, logos, slogans, names of products and services, documentation, other components and content, and the design, selection, and arrangement of content is exclusively our property or, as applicable, its suppliers and licensors, and is protected by copyright, trademark, and other intellectual property laws. Any unauthorized use of any trademarks, trade dress, copyrighted materials, or any other intellectual property belonging to us or any third party is strictly prohibited and may be prosecuted to the fullest extent of the law. The Site may contain references to third-party marks and copies of third-party copyrighted materials, which are the property of their respective owners.   **Copyright © 2017-2018 Silver Star Brands, Inc. All rights reserved**.

**3.  ** **Compliance with Laws.  **You are responsible for complying with all local, state, and federal laws and regulations that apply to your use of the Site, including all applicable rules regarding online conduct.

**4.  ** **Restrictions on Your Use of the Site.**

a. You may download and print one copy of the Site’s visible content for your own personal noncommercial use as long as you do not modify or delete any copyright, trademark, or other proprietary notices.

b. You may not otherwise copy, reproduce, display, duplicate, sell, publish, post, license, rent, distribute, modify, translate, adapt, reverse-engineer, or create derivative works of the Site or any part of the Site without our prior written consent.

c. You warrant that all information you provide to us in connection with your access to and use of the Site is true, accurate, and complete to the best of your knowledge and belief.

d. You may not use the Site for unlawful purposes.

e. You may not engage in data mining or similar data gathering or extraction activities or retrieve data or other content from the Site for purposes of creating or compiling that content for any purpose.

f. You may not submit inaccurate information via the Site, commit fraud or falsify information in connection with your use of the Site, or act maliciously against our business interests or reputation.

g. You may not access, use, or copy any portion of the Site, including any of its content, through the use of indexing agents, spiders, scrapers, bots, web crawlers, or other automated devices or mechanisms.

h. You may not use the Site to post or transmit any material that contains any viruses, Trojan horses, worms, time bombs, cancelbots, ransomware, malware, adware or other computer programming routines that may damage, interfere with, surreptitiously intercept, or expropriate any system, data, or personal information.

i. User activities that aim to render the Site or associated services inoperable or to make their use more difficult are prohibited.

j. You may not post or send unsolicited messages, chain letters, spam, or junk mail.

**5.  ** **Your Account.**  The Site allows you to order products from us as a “guest” or through an account. However, you will be required to set up an online account in order to use certain features of the Site. If you choose to set up an online account, you will be required to submit certain information in order to set up your account and will be required to establish a username and password. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any information you use in connection with the Site, including your username and password. You will not transfer your account to or share your account with any other person. Your account is personal to you.

**6.**   **Account Suspension, Deactivation, and Termination.**  We may, for any reason, at any time, and in our sole discretion, suspend, deactivate, or terminate your account or your use of the Site, or terminate these Terms, without notice or liability, including: if you breach these Terms; upon any unauthorized use of your username, password, or account; if you act in an abusive manner; if you act in a manner inconsistent with local, state, or federal laws or regulations; or if it becomes no longer commercially viable to provide the Site to you. If we suspend, deactivate, or terminate your account, you may not create another account without our prior written permission. You may terminate your account at any time by contacting us at [help@wdrake.com](mailto:help@wdrake.com) or by selecting that option on the Site where that option is available, but you understand that any User-Generated Content (as defined below) you have provided (for example, product reviews) will both remain in our archives and may continue to be accessible by other Site users. Upon any termination of your account or these Terms you must promptly cease accessing and using the Site.

**7.**   **Order & Payment Information. **All orders of products made available on or ordered using the Site (“ **Products** ”) are subject to the below Terms of Sale. Additionally, purchases of Products must be made by credit or debit card or via PayPal or Amazon Payments (where those options are available).  Information about our collection and use of payment-related information is described in our Privacy Policy. If the credit or debit card information that you submit is incorrect or invalid, your payment will not be processed. We have no responsibility or liability if your credit or debit card is declined by your financial institution. Payments are processed by our PCI-compliant third-party payment processor. If we have invited you to apply for private credit with us, additional terms will apply.

**8.**   **Terms of Sale.**

a.  _Order Acceptance._  All orders of Products are subject to acceptance by us.  We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to refuse or cancel any order for any reason, including the following: limitations on Service availability or quantities of Products available for purchase; inaccuracies or errors in Product descriptions, images, or pricing information; and problems identified by credit and fraud avoidance services. We may also require additional verifications, approvals or other information before accepting any order. After we receive your offer to purchase Products, we will send an order acknowledgment to the email address you provide listing the contents of your requested order. This e-mail serves only as information to the purchaser acknowledging that the order has been received.

b.  _Product Availability._  The prices and availability of Products made available on the Site may change at any time without notice to you. Prices remain valid while they are listed and offered on the Site. Availability of Products may be limited and Products may not be available for immediate delivery. Product colors, measurements, and weights are approximate only and may vary from the representation in the Site. These differences will not constitute a defect in or noncompliance of any Product. Some Products may not be available in certain areas. We reserve the right to modify Product offerings at any time, but we are not obligated to make any modifications to Products that have already been shipped.

c.  _Shipping and Handling._  Shipping and handling are explained in our FAQ at [Shipping](https://www.wdrake.com/link/ecb9a7bd31cf47a69928939f14ceba53.aspx?category=1) and [Handling](https://www.wdrake.com/link/ecb9a7bd31cf47a69928939f14ceba53.aspx?category=2).

d.  _Sales tax.   _Requirements by state can be found at [Ordering Online](https://www.wdrake.com/link/ecb9a7bd31cf47a69928939f14ceba53.aspx?category=0&question=3).

e.  _Title and Risk of Loss._  Title to Products will pass to you when you receive the Products.  We will bear the risk of loss or damage to the Products during shipment to you.

f.  _Resale Prohibited._  Resale of Products purchased through the Site is prohibited.

g.  _Order Shortages._  If your order is incomplete upon delivery, please notify us immediately. Any claims for order shortages must be submitted to us within seven days of your receipt of the shipment.

h.  _Order Cancellations._  Order cancellations are at our sole discretion. Our goal is to ship orders promptly, so it is often not possible to cancel an order once it is processed. If you wish to cancel an order, please submit your request via your online account (where that option is available) or contact our customer service department at [help@wdrake.com](mailto:help@wdrake.com), [1-855-202-7393](tel:+18552027393), or [Here](https://www.wdrake.com/link/8df04a70b63b4765a023bf3c691debba.aspx) to see whether we can change, cancel or correct the order before it ships.

i.  _Return Policy.  _Your purchase is subject to our return policy which can be found at [Returns](https://www.wdrake.com/link/ecb9a7bd31cf47a69928939f14ceba53.aspx?category=5).

**9.**   **Buyer’s Club.**  To enroll in our rewards program, you must contact us at [1-855-202-7393](tel:+18552027393) and additional terms and eligibility criteria may apply. You are responsible for keeping your contact information and payment information up to date.

**10.**   **Indemnification.**  You will indemnify, defend, and hold harmless Company Parties from and against all losses, claims, liabilities, demands, complaints, actions, damages, judgments, settlements, fines, penalties, expenses, and costs (including without limitation reasonable attorneys’ fees) that arise out of or in connection with: your access to or use of the Site; your misuse of any material, data, or other information downloaded or otherwise obtained from the Site; your purchase of Products using the Site; your submission of User-Generated Content; or your breach of these Terms. We reserve, and you grant to us, the exclusive right to assume the defense and control of any matter subject to indemnification by you.

**11.**   **User-Generated Content.**

a. The Site may allow you to create, post, transmit, upload, distribute, submit, or otherwise provide comments, data, text, images, video, audio, and other content via the Site, including by submitting product reviews, and to respond to content provided by others (together, “ **User-Generated Content** ”). User-Generated Content is neither generated nor controlled by us. We are not responsible for any User-Generated Content. You are responsible for all User-Generated Content that you provide and for the legality, originality, and appropriateness thereof.

b. By providing User-Generated Content you warrant that you are the creator or owner of that User-Generated Content or that you otherwise have the rights, permissions, and consents necessary to provide that User-Generated Content to us and to allow us to use that User-Generated Content as permitted by these Terms and that any User-Generated Content you provide will not cause us to violate any law or regulation. By providing User-Generated Content, you agree not to claim that any use of that User-Generated Content by us or any third party infringes or violates your or any other person’s intellectual property rights, rights of privacy, rights of publicity, or other right. You retain any copyright or other intellectual property right you may have in User-Generated Content that you provide, subject to the license granted to us below.

c. Please keep in mind that any User-Generated Content that you provide will be publicly available via the Site. You must maintain a polite, pleasant, and respectful environment. User-Generated Content that harasses, abuses, stalks, threatens, or otherwise violates the legal rights of others is prohibited. User-Generated Content must be relevant to the applicable topic (for example, the applicable product listing). User-Generated Content that is defamatory, indecent, pornographic, obscene, or otherwise objectionable or harmful is prohibited. You may not create a false identity, hide your true identity, or impersonate or represent any person other than yourself. You may not provide any other person’s private or confidential information without that person’s permission. If you delete or replace User-Generated Content that you have provided (where that option is available), you understand that it may remain in our archives and that users who have accessed that User-Generated Content may continue to have access to and use it.

d. User-Generated Content is not monitored. We reserve the right, but do not have the obligation, to review User-Generated Content and its submission. We also reserve the right, but do not have the obligation, at any time for any reason, to prescreen User-Generated Content, to edit, redact, and otherwise modify User-Generated Content, to reorganize and recategorize User-Generated Content, and to delete User-Generated Content from the Site. We have no obligation to archive or otherwise store any User-Generated Content. We reserve the right to impose limits on Site features (e.g., the ability to provide User-Generated Content) and to restrict your access to all or parts of the Site at any time for any reason, including upon a breach of these Terms.

e. If you provide User-Generated Content, you grant us a perpetual, irrevocable, transferable, assignable, sublicensable, royalty-free, fully paid-up, worldwide license to copy, reproduce, implement, modify, adapt, reformat, translate, excerpt, prepare derivative works of, store, publish, perform, display, license, sell, exploit, and otherwise use and distribute (in all media and methods now known or later developed) that User-Generated Content for any purpose, including developing, manufacturing, and marketing products and services. You understand that this license allows us to make User-Generated Content you provide to other persons and entities, including other users of the Site. You understand that this license allows us to use User-Generated Content to develop and market products and services.

f. If you believe that anything on the Site infringes any copyright that you own or control, please follow the process described below. If you believe that anything on the Site violates another law or regulation or any provision of these Terms, please notify us of that violation at [help@wdrake.com](mailto:help@wdrake.com).

**12.**   **Copyright Policy.**  We respect the intellectual property rights of others and we ask that our users do the same. In accordance with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (“ **DMCA** ”), located at 17 U.S.C. § 512, and other applicable laws, we strive to expeditiously remove any infringing material from the Site if we become aware of the same. It is our policy to terminate repeat infringers' use of the Site. If you believe that anything on the Site infringes any copyright that you own or control, please provide our designated agent with a notice that contains the following information:

  * A description of the copyrighted work(s) that you claim have been infringed;
  * A description of the allegedly infringing material, including its location on the Site;
  * A statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law;
  * Your email address, telephone number, and mailing address;
  * A statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your notice is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or are authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf; and
  * An electronic or physical signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the copyright owner.

Your notice must meet the then-current requirements implemented by the DMCA. Contact information for our designated agent for notice of claims of copyright infringement is:

Corporate Creations Network Inc.

4650 W. Spencer Street

Appleton, WI 54914

Phone: 920-968-7701

Email: contactus@corpcreations.com

**13.**   **Feedback.**  We welcomes comments regarding the Site. If you submit comments or feedback to us regarding the Site, they will not be considered or treated as confidential. We may use any comments and feedback that you send us in our discretion and without attribution or compensation to you.

**14.**   **Third-Party Websites.**  The Site may link to, or be linked to, websites not maintained or controlled by us. Those links are provided as a convenience and we are not responsible for examining or evaluating the content or accuracy of, and does not warrant or endorse, any third-party website or any products or services made available through those websites. Please take care when leaving the Site to visit a third-party website. You should read the terms of use and privacy policy for each website that you visit.

**15.**   **Linking to the Site.  **If you operate a website and are interested in linking to the Site: (a) the link must be a text-only link and clearly marked; (b) the link must “point” to the URL “www.wdrake.com” and not to any other page; (c) the link and its use must be in connection with a website of appropriate subject matter; (d) the link and its use must not, nor have the potential to, damage or dilute the goodwill associated with our name and trademarks; (e) the link and its use must not create the false appearance that any program, person, or entity is associated with or sponsored by us; and (f) the link, when activated by a user, must display the Site full-screen and not within a frame. We reserves the right to revoke consent to link to the Site at any time in its sole discretion, either by amending these Terms or through other notice.

**16.**   **Force Majeure.**  We will not be liable to you for any delay or other failure to perform under these Terms that is due to causes beyond our control, including acts of God, acts of a public enemy, terrorism, civil disorders, acts of the United States of America or any state, territory or political division thereof, fires, floods, earthquakes, blizzards, and other extraordinary elements of nature.

**17.**   **Disputes.**  These Terms are governed by the laws of the state of Wisconsin, without regards for its conflict of law principles. Venue is exclusively in the state or federal courts, as applicable, located in Winnebago County, Wisconsin, with respect to any dispute arising under these Terms unless otherwise determined by us in its sole discretion and the parties expressly agree to the exclusive jurisdiction of those courts. The United Nations Convention for the International Sale of Goods does not apply.

**18.  Arbitration Agreement; Class Waiver; Waiver of Trial by Jury.**Please read the following paragraphs carefully because they require you to arbitrate disputes with us and limit the manner in which you can seek relief from us.  ARBITRATION NOTICE: THESE Terms CONTAIN A BINDING ARBITRATION PROVISION.  YOU AGREE THAT, EXCEPT FOR CERTAIN TYPES OF DISPUTES DESCRIBED BELOW, ALL DISPUTES BETWEEN YOU AND COMPANY WILL BE RESOLVED BY MANDATORY BINDING ARBITRATION AND YOU WAIVE ANY RIGHT TO PARTICIPATE IN A CLASS ACTION LAWSUIT OR CLASS-WIDE ARBITRATION.

a. Applicability. Any dispute, claim, or controversy arising out of or relating to these Terms, including the breach, termination, enforcement, interpretation, or validity of these Terms (together, “Disputes”), will be resolved by binding arbitration on an individual basis as described in these Terms (this “Arbitration Agreement”). But, in the event of any actual, alleged, or threatened violation of confidentiality or violation of our intellectual property or other proprietary rights, we may immediately resort to court proceedings in a court of competent jurisdiction in order to seek immediate injunctive relief without posting bond, proving damages, or meeting any similar requirement. Any institution of any action for injunctive relief will not constitute a waiver of the right or obligation of either party to submit any claim seeking relief other than injunctive relief to arbitration. This Arbitration Agreement applies to you; us; our affiliates; Company’s and its affiliates’ respective directors, officers, owners, employees, contractors, consultants, agents, representatives, predecessors in interest, successors in interest, and assigns; authorized and unauthorized users or beneficiaries of the Site; and any third-party beneficiaries.

_b. Arbitrator._  Arbitration proceedings will be administered by JAMS/Endispute (“ **JAMS** ”) before an arbitrator selected pursuant to the JAMS rules. The decision of the arbitrator will be final and binding. Any final award or judgment may be filed and enforced in any court of competent jurisdiction. The parties will share equally in the costs assessed for the arbitration and each party will bear its own attorneys’ fees and costs. Any arbitration proceeding may not be consolidated or joined with any other proceeding and will not proceed as a class action.  **The parties understand that they would have had a right or opportunity to litigate Disputes through a court, to have a judge or jury decide their case, and to participate in a class action or other proceeding involving multiple claimants, but they have instead chosen to have all Disputes decided through individual arbitration.**

_c. Place; Federal Arbitration Act._  The place of arbitration will be Winnebago County, Wisconsin, unless otherwise agreed to in writing by all parties to the arbitration. This Arbitration Agreement evidences a transaction involving interstate commerce and the Federal Arbitration Act, 9 U.S.C. Sections 1-16, will govern the interpretation, enforcement, and proceedings pursuant to this Arbitration Agreement.

_d. Confidentiality._  Any and all actions taken under this Arbitration Agreement, including all filings, orders, judgments, and awards made in any arbitration proceeding, are confidential and may not be disclosed to any third party.

_e. Time Limitation on Claims._  Arbitration proceedings must be initiated within one year after any Dispute arises; otherwise, the Dispute is permanently barred.

**19.  Assignment.** We may assign our rights and delegate our duties under these Terms at any time to any party without notice to you. You may not assign your rights or delegate your duties under these Terms without our prior written consent.

**20.  Third-Party Beneficiaries.** These Terms do not confer any rights, remedies, or benefits upon any person other than you and us, except that our affiliates are third-party beneficiaries of these Terms.

**21.  DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES.** THE SITE IS PROVIDED “AS IS,” “AS AVAILABLE,” AND WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. COMPANY MAKES COMMERCIALLY REASONABLE EFFORTS TO ENSURE THAT ALL DATA, INFORMATION, AND MATERIAL ON THE SITE (EXCLUDING ANY USER-GENERATED CONTENT) IS ACCURATE AND RELIABLE, BUT NEITHER ACCURACY NOR RELIABILITY CAN BE GUARANTEED. COMPANY DOES NOT GUARANTEE THE QUALITY, COMPLETENESS, TIMELINESS, OR AVAILABILITY OF THE SITE. COMPANY DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT ANY DEFECTS IN THE SITE WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THE SITE OR THE SERVERS THAT MAKE THE SITE AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL CONDITIONS OR COMPONENTS. COMPANY IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS ON THE SITE. THE COMPANY DOES NOT PROVIDE MEDICAL SERVICES AND NEITHER THE SITE NOR ANY PRODUCTS ARE INTENDED TO BE A SUBSTITUTE FOR PROFESSIONAL MEDICAL ADVICE, DIAGNOSIS, OR TREATMENT.

TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, COMPANY EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND WITH RESPECT TO THE SITE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THOSE REGARDING AVAILABILITY, QUALITY, ACCURACY, MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR ANY USE OR PURPOSE, COMPATIBILITY WITH ANY STANDARDS OR USER REQUIREMENTS, TITLE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT. COMPANY HAS NO RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE TIMELINESS, DELETION, MISDELIVERY, OR FAILURE TO STORE ANY USER COMMUNICATION.

WE DO NOT WARRANT OR ENDORSE ANY USER-GENERATED CONTENT. ALL USER-GENERATED CONTENT IS SOLELY THE RESPONSIBILITY OF THE PERSON WHO PROVIDED THAT USER-GENERATED CONTENT.

WE MAKE NO REPRESENTATION THAT THE SITE IS APPROPRIATE OR AVAILABLE FOR USE IN LOCATIONS OTHER THAN THE UNITED STATES. IF YOU CHOOSE TO ACCESS THE SITE FROM LOCATIONS OTHER THAN THE UNITED STATES, YOU DO SO AT YOUR OWN RISK AND YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR COMPLYING WITH APPLICABLE LAWS AND REGULATIONS.

YOUR USE OF THE SITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK AND YOU, ALONE, ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER HARDWARE, SOFTWARE, SYSTEMS, AND NETWORKS, ANY LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY INFORMATION FROM THE SITE, AND ANY OTHER DAMAGE THAT MAY BE INCURRED.

NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU FROM COMPANY OR IN ANY MANNER FROM THE SITE CREATES ANY WARRANTY.

**22.  LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.** TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL COMPANY, ITS AFFILIATES, OR ITS OR THEIR RESPECTIVE DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, OWNERS, EMPLOYEES, CONTRACTORS, REPRESENTATIVES, CONSULTANTS, AGENTS, SUPPLIERS, OR LICENSORS (TOGETHER, “ **COMPANY PARTIES** ”) BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, EXEMPLARY, PUNITIVE, OR CONSEQUENTIAL LOSS OR DAMAGE, OR ANY OTHER LOSS OR DAMAGE OF ANY KIND, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SITE, YOUR ACCESS TO OR USE OF, OR INABILITY TO ACCESS OR USE, THE SITE (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION THE INPUT OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE AND OTHER INFORMATION INTO THE SITE), YOUR ORDERS, OR YOUR USE OF ANY PRODUCTS, WHETHER THE CLAIM IS BASED IN CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), STRICT LIABILITY, WARRANTY, OR OTHERWISE, AND EVEN IF A COMPANY PARTY HAS EXPRESS KNOWLEDGE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF THE LOSS OR DAMAGE.

YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY IS TO STOP ACCESSING AND USING THE SITE AND, WITH REGARDS TO PRODUCTS AND IF ELIGIBLE, REPLACEMENT OF THE APPLICABLE PRODUCT OR, AT COMPANY’S OPTION, REFUND OF THE PRICE PAID FOR THE APPLICABLE PRODUCT. WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, IN NO EVENT WILL COMPANY PARTIES’ LIABILITY TO YOU EXCEED $100, EVEN IF THIS REMEDY FAILS OF ITS ESSENTIAL PURPOSE. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF CERTAIN DAMAGES, SO SOME OF THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS AND LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.

**23.  Interpretation. **These Terms, including our [Privacy Policy](https://www.wdrake.com/link/ecb9a7bd31cf47a69928939f14ceba53.aspx?category=8), are the entire agreement between you and us with respect to your access to and use of the Site (including your purchase of Products using the Site). Our failure to enforce any provision in these Terms will not constitute a waiver of that provision or any other provision. Any waiver of any provision of these Terms will be effective only if in writing and signed by us. If any provision of these Terms is held invalid, void, or unenforceable, that provision will be severed from the remaining provisions and the remaining provisions will remain in full force and effect. The headings in these Terms are for convenience only and do not affect the interpretation of these Terms. These Terms inure to the benefit of our successors and assigns.

**24.  Survival.** Any provisions of these Terms that are intended to survive termination (including any provisions regarding indemnification, limitation of our liability, or dispute resolution) will continue in effect beyond any termination of these Terms or of your access to or use of the Site.

**25.**   **Electronic Communications.**  These Terms and any other documentation, agreements, notices, or communications between you and us may be provided to you electronically to the extent permissible by law. Please print or otherwise save a copy of all documentation, agreements, notices, and other communications for your reference.

**26.**   **Contact Us.**  Please direct any questions and concerns regarding these Terms to us by email at [help@wdrake.com](mailto:help@wdrake.com), by telephone at [1-855-202-7393](tel:+18552027393), or by mail at 250 City Center, Oshkosh, Wisconsin 54906.

### Shipping

Click on the question below to expand the answer

You can ship an order to yourself at a different address. Physical street addresses are preferred to a P.O. Box number. You may not express ship orders to a P.O. Box.

Yes, we have two express shipping methods in addition to the Economy shipping. Express shipping is not available for shipments outside the contiguous US, to P.O. Boxes or for oversized, drop-ship or out-of-stock items. 

  * **Premium:**  Your order will arrive in 3 business days after leaving our warehouse. Delivery occurs Monday through Friday.  **Additional cost: $9.95**
  * **Next Business Day  **(if ordered by 1:00PM Central): Your order will arrive the next day after leaving our warehouse. Delivery occurs Monday through Friday.  **Additional cost: $32.00**

USPS Priority Mail is for customers OUTSIDE THE CONTIGUOUS UNITED STATES ONLY. It is highly recommended that shipments to Alaska, Hawaii, Puerto Rico and U.S. Territories choose Priority Mail Service in order to receive their package in 7-10 business days; otherwise, it can take as much as 2 to 4 weeks.  **Additional cost: $3.99**

Yes, we will ship internationally in addition to APO and FPO addresses as well as Alaska, Hawaii, Puerto Rico, and other US Territories.

We use USPS as our primary delivery agent. In most cases, orders that ship from our distribution center will arrive in approximately 4 to 8 business days. We process all non-personalized, in-stock items within 2 business days of receipt of your order. Allow an additional 2 business days for orders with personalized items. Please use a street address whenever possible; P.O. Boxes may delay delivery.

All items that are in stock will ship together unless they are physically extra large or are drop-ship (direct delivered from another location).

We offer Free Shipping on select items! Look for the “Item Ships Free” indicator on all eligible merchandise to save money. Shipping discount will automatically be deducted at checkout.

Our shipping costs are based on merchandise subtotal. Merchandise eligible for the Free Shipping discount will be deducted from your overall merchandise subtotal when tabulating shipping costs at checkout. You will only be charged shipping and handling for merchandise that is NOT eligible for the Free Shipping discount.

The Free Shipping offer is  **limited to economy shipping only**  and is valid on qualifying merchandise before taxes, fees and discounts. Certain oversized items may include an additional surcharge as indicated on the applicable product page. Offer does not apply to international orders. When selecting multiple shipping addresses, additional charges may apply. Cannot be combined with other offers.

Please see the Shipping Cost table below for standard shipping rates. Please note:

  * Some of our larger items may require additional shipping charges as indicated in the product copy.
  * $4.99 will be added to your shopping cart for each package sent to an additional address.
  * For split shipment orders: All shipping charges are prorated by package on the invoices and your shipping confirmation emails. This is an automatic calculation done by our system at the time the packages are shipped. The combined total of your separate shipping charges will never exceed the original shipping charge authorized during checkout.
  * There may be additional charges for international shipments (see International FAQs).
  * To substantially decrease shipping time, it is recommended that shipments to Alaska, Hawaii, Puerto Rico and US Territories be done via USPS Priority Mail (see “Do you have express shipping?” above for more details)
  * We do ship to APO/FPO addresses.

**Merchandise Subtotal** | **Please Add**  
---|---  
$0.01 - $9.99 | $4.99  
$10.00 - $19.99 | $5.99  
$20.00 - 29.99 | $7.99  
$30.00 - 44.99 | $8.99  
$45.00 - $59.99 | $10.99  
$60.00 - $79.99 | $12.99  
$80 - $99.99 | $14.99  
$100.00 or more | $15.99  
  
### Handling

Click on the question below to expand the answer

Handling helps us maintain the lowest possible prices and shipping charges by offsetting a portion of the cost to process and fulfill your order. We choose not to hide these costs within our shipping chart or cover them by raising the price of our products.

Join our [Buyer's Club](https://www.wdrake.com/link/98c0aab29f3441f0bd009a8dcea7f958.aspx) and receive FREE shipping and 10% discount on all orders.

OR

Sign up for our [Email list](https://www.wdrake.com/link/784a4a7d2e174b978dd9d9ee443f84b3.aspx) and receive special offers!

### Services

Click on the question below to expand the answer

We are pleased to help you create custom products for business gifts, commemoratives and incentive programs. Please call our Customer Service Department at 1-855-202-7393 for details.

### Email

Click on the question below to expand the answer

### Returns

Click on the question below to expand the answer

All returns must be made within 45 days from the date of shipment. We carefully inspect orders prior to shipment; upon receipt, please inspect your purchase and notify us of any damage. We will arrange for a prompt replacement. If you are dissatisfied with any non-personalized merchandise, you may return your purchase for a refund of the merchandise value. Shipping charges will not be reimbursed.

We cannot accept returns on personalized items for reasons other than defects in the material or workmanship.

We also cannot offer refunds on our Clearance items, but would be happy to exchange your item for a credit or replacement.

If you receive a damaged or incorrectly personalized item, or if you are missing an item please contact our Customer Service Department.

**Phone: 1-855-202-7393**

**Monday-Friday 8:00AM - 10:00PM**

**Saturday 8:00AM - 5:00PM**

**Sunday 8:00AM – 5:00PM (Central)**

**Email:** **[help@wdrake.com](mailto:help@wdrake.com)**

**Please allow 24 hours in turn-around time for an email response.**

**Use a Pre-Paid Shipping Label.**

SEND IT BACK TO US

Simply click [Here](https://www.wdrake.com/link/5ee8dce8f27b495184b4fe7490e87439.aspx), fill in your order specifics and personal information, and print the return label.

  1. Repackage items exactly how you received them – boxes, tags, and all
  2. Attach your new shipping label and take your sealed box to any [UPS Location](https://www.ups.com/dropoff?autosubmit) or drop-off box

DONE – WE’LL TAKE IT FROM HERE!

Write down your tracking number and we’ll refund your order within 10 days of receiving it, less $7 for shipping.

EXPECTING AN EXCHANGE?

Place a new order now.

NEED A HAND?

Give us a call at 1-855-202-7393 or email us at [help@walterdrake.com](mailto:help@walterdrake.com).

**Return or exchange using your packing slip.** To return an item, fill in all applicable information on the reverse side of your packing slip and send it to us along with the item. A return shipping label is provided on the packing slip. Use the shipping company of your preference. Please allow us 2-3 weeks for return or exchange to be handled when using this method.

**If you no longer have your packing slip,** please include contact information, item number and price, action desired (refund or replacement), method of payment if needed as well as the reason for returning the merchandise on a separate sheet of paper and mail it along with the item to:

Walter Drake  
Return Goods  
2155 S. Oakwood Rd.  
Oshkosh, WI 54904

### Order Form

Click on the question below to expand the answer

### Security & Privacy

Click on the question below to expand the answer

Your WDrake.com shopping is safe with the use of Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) and Data Encryption Standard (DES) on our online server. To take advantage of secure shopping, you must have an SSL/DES compatible browser such as Netscape or Explorer. By using SSL, all online communications between you and WDrake.com are protected from being intercepted, viewed, or altered by unauthorized parties.

Your shipping and billing address may be used to send you our print catalog or catalogs and direct mail from our affiliated companies that we feel may be of interest to you. We may also trade your name and mailing address with other reputable mail order companies. If you do not want your name traded with or rented to other companies, please contact our Customer Service Department.

**Phone: 1-855-202-7393**  
Monday-Friday 8:00AM - 10:00PM  
Saturday 8:00AM - 5:00PM  
Sunday 8:00AM – 5:00PM (Central)

**Email:  **[ **help@wdrake.com**](mailto:help@wdrake.com)  
Please allow 24 hours in turn-around time for an email response.

If you are interested in or have questions regarding public relations information from Walter Drake, please send an email to: [help@wdrake.com](mailto:help@wdrake.com).

**Privacy Policy**

  **Last Updated: July 11, 2018**

This Privacy Policy describes the information collected through this website (“ **Site** ”) and how that information is used and shared. This Privacy Policy also explains your rights and choices regarding your personal information, how we communicate changes to this Privacy Policy, and how you may contact us regarding questions or issues with respect to anything contained in this Privacy Policy.

Silver Star Brands, Inc., doing business as Walter Drake (“ **Company** ,” “ **we** ,” “ **us** ,” or “ **our** ”), and its suppliers may collect or receive the types of information described below in connection with your access to and use of the Site (together, “ **Collected Information** ”).

**By accessing or using the Site or by accepting our  [Terms of Use](https://www.wdrake.com/link/ecb9a7bd31cf47a69928939f14ceba53.aspx?category=0&question=12), you (“you”) agree that you have read and understand this Privacy Policy.**

**This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and made a part of our  [Terms of Use](https://www.wdrake.com/link/ecb9a7bd31cf47a69928939f14ceba53.aspx?category=0&question=12). We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. All changes will be effective immediately upon posting to the Site. Material changes will be conspicuously posted on the Site or otherwise communicated to you.**

**If you have any questions or concerns about our use of your personal information, please contact us using the contact information provided at the end of this Privacy Policy.  **

**Information We Collect and How We Collect It**

The information that we may collect from or about you broadly falls into the following categories: 

  * Information that you voluntarily provide to us, for example, your contact information, payment information, and product reviews.
  * Information that we collect through your use of the Site, for example, account activity, data collected by the servers used to operate the Site (e.g., IP addresses), data collected by cookies, and data collected by analytics and advertising services. 

We will use collected personal information and other Collected Information as described below, including to set up your online account, to process your product orders, and to provide you with information and communications that you request or that we believe are relevant or may be of interest to you, subject to your communications preferences, applicable laws, and the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

**Information that You Voluntarily Provide to Us  **

**Contact Information.**  You can visit and use the Site without voluntarily sharing personal information, but you will be required to provide your contact information to register for an online account and to use certain other features of the Site.We will collect any contact information and other personal information from or about you that you choose to submit to us, which may include your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, and payment information. For example, we collect your contact information when you create an online account, in connection with your purchase of products on the Site, in receiving and fulfilling information requests, and when you respond to communications from us (e.g., surveys and promotional offers). We will use your contact information as described below, including to set up your online account, to process your orders of product, and to provide you with information and communications that you request or that we believe are relevant or may be of interest to you, subject in each case to your communications preferences, applicable laws, and the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you provide your mobile or other telephone number to us, you consent to receiving telephone calls (both in-person and from automated dialing systems) from us at that telephone number as described below.

**Account Information.**  To create an online account you will need to submit your name and email address and you may be required to select and answer security questions.

**Order & Payment Information. **Purchases of products and gift certificates (if available) using the Site must be made by credit or debit card. All credit and debit card information is provided directly to our PCI-compliant third-party payment processors. We do not store your credit or debit card information after remitting it to our third-party processors. To make a purchase on the Site, you will need to submit your name and your credit or debit card type, number, expiration date, security code, and billing address. If you make a purchase using Amazon Payments, you may need to log in to your Amazon account. Amazon may use Collected Information as described in the [Amazon Payments Privacy Notice](https://pay.amazon.com/us/help/201751600). If you make a purchase using PayPal, you may need to log in to your PayPal account. PayPal may use Collected Information as described in its [PayPal’s Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full). We will maintain a record of the purchases you make using the Site. Our payment processor, Chase Paymentech, may use your payment-related information in accordance with the [Chase Paymentech Privacy Policy](https://www.chasepaymentech.com/privacypolicy/).

**Rewards Program.**  To participate in our rewards program you will need to submit your name, physical address, email address, and telephone number.

**Information We Collect When You Opt In to Marketing Communications.  **If you sign up or otherwise opt in to receive promotions or other communications from us, you will need to submit your email address. You may also provide your physical address. We will use this information to provide you with promotional and other electronic and hard copy communications (e.g., catalogs). You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from us at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in the applicable email and you may opt out of receiving hard copy mailings from us by contacting us using the contact information provided below under “Contact Us.”  We may use third-party email providers to deliver these communications to you.

**User-Generated Content.**  You are responsible for any comments, data, text, images, video, audio, and other content (e.g., product reviews) that you create, post, transmit, upload, distribute, submit, or otherwise provide using the Site (together, “ **User-Generated Content** ”). User-Generated Content you provide is posted on the Site at your own risk. We cannot guarantee that User-Generated Content will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. You understand that any User-Generated Content you provide will be publicly available via the Site. You understand that, even after removal, copies of User-Generated Content that you have provided may remain viewable in cached and archived pages and may have been copied or stored by Internet archives and other Site users. _ _

**Information that We Collect Through Your Use of the Site**

**IP Addresses, Location Data, and Related Data.**  When you visit or use the Site, we may automatically collect certain information from your device. In some countries, including countries in the European Economic Area (“ **EEA** ”), this information may be considered personal information under applicable data protection laws. Specifically, the servers used to operate and provide the Site may collect data pertaining to you and the equipment, software, and communication methods you use to access the Internet and the Site, including Internet protocol (“ **IP** ”) addresses assigned to the computers and other devices from where you access the Internet, your Internet service provider, your device ID number, your approximate geographic location, your browser type, the pages you access on the Site, the websites you access before and after visiting the Site, the length of time you spend on the Site, date and time stamps, and clickstream data. We may use this information to administer the Site and our servers, to generate statistical information, to monitor and analyze Site traffic and usage patterns, to monitor and prevent fraud, to investigate complaints and violations of our policies, and to improve the Site’s content and the products, services, materials, and other content that we describe or make available through the Site. We may combine this information with other Collected Information (including personal information) and information obtained from third parties for the purposes discussed below. The suppliers that we use to provide the Site may collect information about your visits to the Site and other websites. Some of this information may be collected using cookies and similar tracking technologies as explained further below under “Cookies.”

**Cookies.  **The Site may automatically use cookies to track your use of the Site in order to facilitate and enhance the user experience on the Site and for other purposes as described below. “ **Cookies** ” are small pieces of information that are stored on your device’s hard drive by your browser. The Site may use both cookies that we implement and cookies implemented by our suppliers and other third parties. We use cookies to track how you access and use the Site, to learn when and how users visit the Site, to learn how popular Site pages are and aren’t, to learn which search terms are used to find the Site, and to learn which websites direct you to the Site. We also use cookies to help display certain information on the Site and to improve your enjoyment of the Site, for example, by remembering your contact and other information when you access or use the Site. Most browsers automatically accept cookies. You can disable this function, but disabling cookies may impact your use and enjoyment of the Site. Our Site suppliers may use cookies and other tracking technologies, such as pixel tags, to track Site visitors across the Internet to understand how you get to the Site. We do not have access or control over these cookies and this Privacy Policy does not cover the use of third-party cookies.  Due to this automatic collection of data using cookies, we do not honor “do not track” requests. Our use of these technologies fall into the following categories: 

  * _Operationally necessary._  These are cookies that are required for the operation of the Site. For example, these cookies are required to identify irregular website behavior, prevent fraudulent activity, and improve security. They also allow users of the Site to make use of its functions, for example, shopping carts, saved search, and similar functions. Without these cookies, Sites that you have requested cannot be provided. 

  * _Functionality related._  These cookies allow us to offer you enhanced functionality when accessing or using the Site. This may include to remembering choices you make, for example and as applicable, remembering your username, preferences, or settings, remembering if you reacted to something on or through the Site so that you are not asked to do it again, remembering if you have used any feature of the Site before, restricting the number of times you are shown a particular advertisement, remembering your location, and enabling social media components. As described above, you may disable functional cookies, but if you do so then various functions of the Site may be unavailable to you or may not work the way you want them to. 

  * _Performance related._  These cookies assess the performance of the Site, including as part of our analytic practices to help us understand how visitors use and interact with the Site, for example, which pages on our websites users visit most often. These cookies also enable us to personalize content and remember your preferences (e.g., your choice of language, country, or region). These cookies help us improve the way our websites work and provide a better, personalized user experience. Some of our performance-related cookies are managed for us by third parties. However, we don’t allow those third parties to use the cookies for any purpose other than those listed above. 

  * _Advertising or targeted related._  These cookies record your visits to the Site, the pages you have visited on our websites, and the links you have clicked. They gather information about your browsing habits and remember that you have visited a particular website. We and our third-party advertising platforms or networks may use this information to make the Site, its content, and advertisements displayed on our websites more relevant to your interests (this is sometimes called “behavioral” or “targeted” advertising and is further discussed below). These types of cookies are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement and to help measure the effectiveness of advertising campaigns. To find out more about interest-based ads and your choices, please visit the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://digitaladvertisingalliance.org/), the [Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/), the [Interactive Advertising Bureau (IAB) Europe](https://www.iabeurope.eu/), [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/), and [http://www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). 

**Analytics.**  The Site uses third-party analytics tools (e.g., Google Analytics, provided by Google Inc.) to collect and process data (including personal data) about your use of the Site, including when you visit the Site, URLs of the websites that you visit prior to visiting the Site and when you visit those websites, and IP addresses assigned to the devices from where you access the Internet. Our analytics providers may set and read cookies to collect this data and your web browser will automatically send data collected by those cookies to our analytics providers. Our analytics providers use this data to provide us with reports that we will use to improve the Site’s structure and content. For more information on how Google uses collected data, visit [Google’s Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy) and Google’s page on ["How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps"](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners). To prevent this data from being used by Google Analytics, follow the instructions to download and install the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) for each web browser you use. Using the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on will not prevent Company from using other analytics tools and will not prevent data from being sent to the Site itself or to Google. For more information about how Google Analytics uses cookies to measure user interactions on websites, visit [Google Analytics Cookie Usage on Websites](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage). You may disable cookies as discussed above, but that may impact your use and enjoyment of the Site. ** **

**Advertising Networks, Personalized Advertising, Remarketing, and Retargeting.  **From time to time the Site may use or participate in advertising networks and related advertising services that are managed and provided by third-party advertising servers, advertising agencies, technology vendors, and research firms, including, as discussed below, Google AdWords. These services collect information about your visits to and interactions with the Site and other websites and will use that information to target advertisements for goods and services. The information collected may be associated with your personal information. These targeted advertisements may appear on the Site or on other websites. Advertising networks often gather data about consumers who view advertisements to make inferences about a consumer’s interests and preferences, which enables their computers to deliver advertisements directly targeted to the consumer’s specific interests. This practice is often referred to as “online behavioral advertising.” For example, a third-party advertising network might collect the type of Internet browser you use, the type of computer operating system you use, the domain name of a website you visit, whether or not you visit specific pages of the Site and other websites, the location of your Internet service provider, the date and time of a visit to a website, and other interactions between you and a website. 

We use Google AdWords, an online advertising service provided by Google, to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on the Site. Google uses your Internet searches, cookies, and similar identifiers (e.g., pixel tags) to collect information about your visits to the Site and your interaction with our products and services to generate targeted advertisements to you on other websites that you visit across the Internet. To opt out of remarketing advertising provided through Google, to customize your ad preferences, or to limit Google’s collection or use this information, visit [Google’s Safety Center](https://www.google.com/safetycenter/tools) and [Google’s Ad Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads) and follow [Google’s personalized ad opt-out instructions](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en&ref_topic=7048998). Opting out will not affect your use of the Site. 

**To change your preferences with respect to certain online ads and to obtain more information about third-party ad networks and online behavioral advertising, please visit the  **[ **National Advertising Initiative Consumer opt-out page**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) **  or the **[ **Digital Advertising Alliance Self-Regulatory Program**](http://www.aboutads.info/) **.**  Please remember that changing your settings with individual browsers or ad networks will not necessarily carry over to other browsers or ad networks. As a result, depending on the opt-outs you request, you may still see our ads from time to time. 

**Single Sign-On.**  You may sign up for and log into your account using your Amazon.com account by providing your Amazon log-in information on the Site when prompted. If you choose to use this feature, Company may access, handle, and store information that you have provided through Amazon and make that information available on the Site. This feature may require us to implement cookies, plug-ins, and application protocol interfaces (APIs) provided by Amazon to facilitate those communications and features. We do not and cannot control any policies or terms of any third-party service, including those of Amazon. All information you have provided to Amazon is subject to the [Amazon Privacy Notice](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=201909010). ** **

**Social Media.**  The Site may allow you to connect to and share information with various social media platforms, for example, Facebook. These features may require us to implement cookies, plug-ins, and application protocol interfaces (APIs) provided by those social media platforms to facilitate those communications and features. We may share information that you provide us or that we may collect about your use of the Site with those platforms and that information will be subject to their privacy policies. We encourage you to review those platforms’ privacy policies: see [Facebook’s Data Policy](https://www.facebook.com/full_data_use_policy). In addition, by choosing to use any third-party social media platform or choosing to share content or communications with any social media platform, you allow us to share information with the designated social media platform. We cannot control any policies or terms of such third party platform. As a result, we cannot be responsible for any use of your information or content by a third party platform, which you use at your own risk. 

The Site may also use the advertising services and networks offered by those social media platforms to deliver advertising content. Use of these services requires social media platforms to implement cookies or pixel tags to deliver ads to you while you are logged into the platform. 

If you do not wish a social media platform to collect information relating to you via the Site, we suggest that you: (a) hide social media platform plug-ins using an ad blocker; (b) always log off completely from the social media platform before visiting other websites and delete all related cookies; and, (c) where the option made available by the social media platform, disable the advertising services and networks operated by that platform. 

The Company is active on social media, including Facebook. You have the opportunity to comment on those social media platforms regarding Company and the products and services we offer. We reserve the right to post on our websites and social media pages any comments or content that you post on our social media pages. ** **

**Embedded Content.  **The Site may incorporate content, including feeds scripts embedded in the Site’s code and visible content (for example, videos), provided by third parties. In some cases, those third parties collect data about how you interact with their content. For example, YouTube may collect or otherwise have access to usage data on videos embedded on the Site as described in [YouTube’s Privacy Policy](https://www.youtube.com/yt/about/policies/#community-guidelines). 

**How We Use and Share Collected Information  **

In addition to the uses described above, we and our suppliers may use and disclose Collected Information as described below. We do not use, sell, rent, or disclose Collected Information except as stated in this Privacy Policy and as permitted by applicable law. This Privacy Policy describes some specific ways that we share your data. However, unless you give us your permission, we generally will not share your personal information with third parties except as described below. 

**Purpose Collected.**  We will use and share your personal information and other Collected Information for the purpose for which it was collected, for example, to process your orders for products, in connection with your account and payment, and to provide you with information and communications that you request. If you place an order through the Site, we will use Collected Information to communicate with you regarding your order. In accordance with your preferences, your location information will be used to add location information to your account, if applicable, and to understand where our users are located and to determine the proper sales tax. If you contact us for support or assistance in using the Site, we may use Collected Information to determine whether or not your system meets the minimum requirements needed to access and use the Site and otherwise to contact you regarding your request. 

**Communication with You.**  When you contact our customer service department we may ask you to provide or confirm Collected Information so that we can better serve you. We may use Collected Information to notify you of changes made to the Site (for example, changes to our [Terms of Use](https://www.wdrake.com/link/ecb9a7bd31cf47a69928939f14ceba53.aspx?category=0&question=12) or this Privacy Policy) and, if you sign up or otherwise opt in to receive communications from us, to send you promotional materials and other communications as described above. If you provide us with your telephone number, we may call you at that telephone number in response to your orders, questions, or comments or for customer service purposes. If you register for an account on the Site, we will use Collected Information to communicate with you regarding your account. You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from us at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in the applicable email or by contacting us using the contact information provided below under “Contact Us.” 

**Sharing Collected Information with Our Suppliers.  **We may share Collected Information with our Site management and hosting suppliers, payment processors, marketing and public relations service providers, email service suppliers, and other suppliers as necessary for us to provide the Site and our products and services to you, to engage in the use and sharing of Collected Information as permitted by this Privacy Policy, and as may be otherwise permitted by applicable law. Our suppliers are authorized to and may use and disclose Collected Information as necessary for them to provide the applicable services to us and as provided by their own privacy policies as noted above. 

**Sharing Collected Information with Our Partners.**  We may share certain aggregated Collected Information, such as zip codes and products purchased, with our affiliates and with the third-party manufacturers and providers of the products that we sell to help those third parties learn about the sales and success of their products. ** **

**Sharing Collected Information with Other Third Parties.**  We may share, rent, license, or sell Collected Information with third parties who have or offer products or services we think may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving communications from any such third party pursuant to such third party’s policies. We do not control any third party or their policies. ** **

**Aggregate Data.**  We may aggregate personal information and other Collected Information to create aggregate data on Site users, which describes users as a group but does not reveal the identity of individual users. We may use aggregate data to understand Site users’ needs, to determine Site user demographics and usage patterns, to determine what kinds of products and services we can provide, and to improve and enrich our products, our services, and the Site. 

**Evaluation and Improvement of the Site.**  We may use Collected Information: to analyze, develop, and improve the content, materials, products, and services that we make available through the Site and the Site’s functionality; to inform marketing and communication plans and strategies; to evaluate user needs and customize Site content, promotional emails, and your browsing experience; and for other legitimate and lawful business purposes. 

**To Protect Company and Others.**  We may share your personal information with law enforcement, regulatory authorities, courts with competent jurisdictions, emergency services, and other necessary third parties for legal, protection, security, and safety purposes, including: (a) to comply with laws or regulatory requirements and to respond to lawful requests and legal process; (b) to perform credit checks, report or collect debts owed; (c) to protect our rights and property, our agents and customers, and others, including to enforce our agreements, policies, and terms and to protect our network and physical assets; and (d) to protect the safety of our employees, agents, and customers, and any other person. ** **

**Business Transactions.**  We may choose to buy or sell assets from time to time. We may share Collected Information in connection with the evaluation of those transactions. We may transfer Collected Information if we enter into those transactions. Also, if we (or our assets) are acquired or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control or reorganization, personal information and other Collected Information could be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party. 

**With Your Consent.**  With your consent, we may share your personal information in ways not specifically described in this Privacy Policy. 

**Legal Basis for Processing Your Personal Information (EEA Only)** ** **

If you are an individual from the EEA, our legal basis for collecting and using personal information will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it. However, we will normally collect personal information from you only where: (a) we have your consent to do so; (b) where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you (e.g., to deliver services you have requested); or (c) where the processing is in our or a third party’s legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms. In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal information from you or may otherwise need the personal information to protect your vital interests or those of another person. 

If we ask you to provide personal information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and will advise you whether or not the provision of your personal information is mandatory, as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your personal information. Similarly, if we collect and use your personal information in reliance on our or a third party’s legitimate interests that are not already described in this Privacy Policy, we will make clear to you at the relevant time what those legitimate interests are. 

If you have any questions about or need further information concerning the legal basis on which we collect and use your personal information, please contact us using the contact details provided further below provided below under “Contact Us.” 

**International Transfers of Your Personal Information**  

In operating the Site, your personal information may be transferred to, stored in, and processed in countries other than the country in which you are resident. Those countries may have data protection laws that are different from those of your country and, in some cases, may not be as protective. Specifically, our Site servers and some of our service providers are located in the United States and our affiliated companies and third-party service providers and partners operate around the world. This means that when we collect your personal information we may process it in other countries. We have, however, taken appropriate safeguards to require that your personal information will remain protected in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Information Security  **

Company does not guarantee that loss, misuse, or alteration of Collected Information will not occur, but we take appropriate technical and organizational security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of Collected Information under our control. Specifically, on our shopping cart and payment pages, Secure Socket Layers technology is used to encrypt information passed between your browser and our systems. While we are focused on the security of your personal information and follow strict standards, processes and procedures that designed to protect your personal information, you must remember that the Internet is a global communications vehicle open to threats, viruses and intrusions from others and so we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that we will be able to protect your personal information at all times and in all circumstances. 

If you become aware of any breach of Site security or this Privacy Policy, please notify us at [privacy@wdrake.com](mailto:privacy@wdrake.com) immediately. If our security system is breached, we will notify you of the breach only if and to the extent required under applicable law. 

**How Long We Retain Your Personal Information**  

We will retain your personal information for as long as is needed to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (e.g., tax, accounting, or other legal requirements). When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize it, or, if that is not possible (e.g., because your personal information has been stored in back-up archives), we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible. 

For personal information that we process on behalf of our customers, we will retain that personal information in accordance with the terms of our agreement with them, subject to applicable law. 

**Your Rights and Choices Regarding Your Personal Information**  

You have the following data protection rights:

  * If you wish to access, correct, update or request deletion of your personal information, you can do so at any time by visiting your account or contacting us at [privacy@wdrake.com](mailto:privacy@wdrake.com). 

  * You have the right to opt out of marketing communications we send you at any time. You can exercise this right by clicking on the “unsubscribe” or “opt out” link in the marketing e-mails we send you. To opt out of other forms of marketing, such as postal marketing or telemarketing, if applicable, then please contact us using the contact information provided below under “Contact Us.” 

  * Similarly, if we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent. 

  * In addition, if you are a resident of the European Union, you can object to the processing of your personal information, you can ask us to restrict processing of your personal information, and you can request portability of your personal information. You can exercise these rights by contacting us using the contact information provided below under “Contact Us.” 

  * You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information please contact your local data protection authority. Contact information for data protection authorities in the EEA, Switzerland, and certain non-European countries (including the United States and Canada) are available [here](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm). 

  * For details on how to manage your preferences for cookies and tracking technologies within your web browser, please read the information provided above under "Cookies." 

We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws. 

**Access by Children**  

The Site is not directed at children under 16 years of age. Company does not knowingly collect or use information from children under 16 through the Site. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 16 has provided personal information to us through the Site, please contact us at [privacy@wdrake.com](mailto:privacy@wdrake.com) and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete that information. 

**Third-Party Websites** ** **

The Site may link to, or be linked to, websites not maintained or controlled by us. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third parties or any third-party websites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any third-party websites or to any personal or other information that you may provide to third parties. You should read the privacy policy for each website that you visit. 

**Contact Us**  

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, contact us by email at [privacy@wdrake.com](mailto:privacy@wdrake.com), by telephone at [855-202-7393](tel:+18552027393), or by mail at 250 City Center, Oshkosh, Wisconsin 54906.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, California residents have the right under certain circumstances to receive, once per calendar year, information about third parties with whom we have shared information about you or your family for the marketing purposes of those third parties during the previous calendar year, a description of the categories of personal information shared, and a description of the nature of the business with whom it was shared. 

To make such a request, please send an email to [privacy@wdrake.com](mailto:privacy@walterdrake.com "Walter Drake email") or write us at Walter Drake, 250 City Center, Oshkosh, WI 54906-0001. Please include the phrase “California Privacy Request” in the subject line of any email request. Please also identify the domain name of the website you are inquiring about and include your name, email address, and mailing address in any request.

We will respond to you within a reasonable time of your request.

### Toy Safety

Click on the question below to expand the answer

Safety is a priority for the Walter Drake Company. All toys sold by Walter Drake meet toy industry safety standards including the ASTM F963-96A regulation regarding lead content in paint. 

### International

Click on the question below to expand the answer

Walter Drake fulfills online international orders through our partner, Borderfree. Simply add items to your order and click on international check out to complete your order. You will see your total landed price including all duties, taxes, shipping and handling charges in your currency before you finalize your order. You will pay Borderfree the total amount for your order in your currency (which means that they will bill your credit card) and we will ensure that products get right to your door. If you have any questions about your international order, please contact our Customer Service Department.

**Phone: 1-855-202-7393**  
Monday-Friday 8:00AM - 10:00PM  
Saturday 8:00AM - 5:00PM  
Sunday 8:00AM – 5:00PM (Central)

**Email:  **[ **help@wdrake.com**](mailto:help@wdrake.com)  
Please allow 24 hours in turn-around time for an email response. All responses to customer service questions will be in English

Determining your duty rates depends on many factors (Product, Country in which the product was manufactured, etc.). To know the exact duty charges before you buy, simply add items to your order and check out through our "International Check Out." You will see the exact duty charges prior to submitting the order.

The tax rate applied depends on your ship-to destination. Please refer to the following chart to determine the relevant rate for a Canadian order.

Province of Delivery | GST    | PST    | HST  
---|---|---|---  
Alberta |  5% |  - |  -  
BC |  5% |  - |  -  
Manitoba |  5% |  - |  -  
New Brunswick |  - |  - |  13%  
Newfoundland & Labrador    |  - |  - |  13%  
Northwest Territories |  6% |  - |  -  
Nova Scotia |  - |  - |  15%  
Nunavut |  5% |  - |  -  
Ontario |  - |  - |  13%  
Prince Edward Island |  - |  - |  14%  
Quebec |  5% |  - |  -  
Saskatchewan |  5% |  - |  -  
Yukon Territory |  5% |  - |  -  
  
Shipping and handling charges depend on the size and weight of your package and your ship-to destination. To know the exact shipping and handling charges before you buy, simply add items to your order and check out through our International Check Out. Also included will be Handling. This is a flat fee to help defray the cost of handpicking your order. Handling will be included in the shipping and handling fee when you check out. We will tell you the exact charges for your desired item(s) prior to submitting the order.

Walter Drake offers the following shipping options to international buyers:

Shipping Method

| 

When in-stock items will arrive  
  
---|---  
  
Standard

| 

Canada Post, 5-17 business days (Monday through Friday, do not count weekends)*  
  
Expedited

| 

DHL Express, 4-8 business days (Monday through Friday, do not count weekends)*  

*Add 2-3 days for orders with personalized items.

Your order will be billed to your credit card by our international service provider, Borderfree. "BF*WalterDrake*" will appear as the billing company.

The customer is billed when the order leaves the Borderfree HUB. 

Real-time exchange rates are applied to your orders. The rate charged to you is a guaranteed amount - this will not change once you accept an order. To know the exact price before you buy, simply add items to your order and check out through our International Check Out. You will see the exact price for your order in your currency before you finalize the order.

Within 24 hours of placing your order, you will receive an order confirmation email. When your package clears our international facility and is on its way to you, you will receive a shipment notification email that will include a link to track your package. You may also track your international package directly through the Borderfree website [here](https://services.fiftyone.com/tracking.srv). All other inquiries should be directed to [help@wdrake.com](mailto:help@wdrake.com). All responses to customer service questions will be in English.

All returns must be made within 45 days from the date that you receive the shipment. Personalized items cannot be returned for reasons other than defects in material or workmanship. If you have any damaged, missing, or incorrectly personalized item(s), call, write, or email our [Customer Service Department](https://www.wdrake.com/link/8df04a70b63b4765a023bf3c691debba.aspx). Information on how to do a return is listed on the back of the packing slip that is included with every shipment.

### Product Search & Availability

Click on the question below to expand the answer

Yes, we will let you know about availability before you add a product to your cart. Additionally, once you review your shopping cart, inventory availability will be listed for each of your products.

Yes! Please call our customer service department at 1-855-202-7393 Monday-Friday 8:00AM - 10:00PM, Saturday 8:00AM - 5:00PM and Sunday 8:00AM – 5:00PM (Central) to check the availability of the product you wish to order.

Enter the item number, the product name, or a description of the product in the search box at the top of this page. Click the Search button.

### Personalized Merchandise

Click on the question below to expand the answer

You can review personalization when you are on the [Shopping Cart page](https://www.wdrake.com/link/5751eb01a6ed40f2a6f80ba1ee4a6bf7.aspx). If the personalization is incorrect, click on the Edit button and make any changes you need.

All in-stock merchandise will ship together. If your order contains personalized and non-personalized products, the in-stock merchandise should ship together.

### Auto Refill

Click on the question below to expand the answer

The Auto Refill program is an automatic delivery service which allows you to receive [select products](https://www.wdrake.com/link/116239b871d646a59533f7566cafeca0.aspx) you use on a regular basis every 30, 60, 90 or 120 days depending on the item. No need to worry about reordering. Your shipping is FREE on subsequent orders so you save both time and money when you sign up.

To shop Auto Refill items, click [here](https://www.wdrake.com/link/116239b871d646a59533f7566cafeca0.aspx).

When you use Auto Refill, the price never goes up. By avoiding price increases online or in the catalog, you save money by getting the same price you paid in your initial order. Even when you receive a special promotion or sale price, the price stays the same on all your future Auto Refill orders.

On your initial order you will pay the regular shipping and handling price as noted in our shipping and handling chart. On all subsequent refill orders your shipment is FREE.

In order to make any changes such as the quantity of your delivery, the delivery date, your delivery address, please contact our Customer Service Department.

 **Phone: 1-855-202-7393**  
Monday-Friday 8:00AM – 10:00PM  
Saturday 8:00AM – 5:00PM  
Sunday 8:00AM – 5:00PM (Central)

 **Email:  [ **help@wdrake.com**](mailto:help@wdrake.com)**  
Please allow 24 hours turn-around time for an email response.

If you wish to cancel your program for any reason, please contact our Customer Service Department.

 **Phone: 1-855-202-7393**  
Monday-Friday 8:00AM – 10:00PM  
Saturday 8:00AM – 5:00PM  
Sunday 8:00AM – 5:00PM (Central)

 **Email:  [ **help@wdrake.com**](mailto:help@wdrake.com)**  
Please allow 24 hours turn-around time for an email response.

Unless modified by the customer, the credit card used to set up the initial Auto Refill order will be charged for subsequent orders. Subsequent orders will be authorized 1-2 days prior to shipment and charged when shipped. Only credit or debit cards can be used as payment for Auto Refill orders. Gift vouchers, checks, and PayPal will not be accepted at this time. Product prices will reflect the pricing of initial order and remain the same on all future orders. Auto Refill is not available for international orders. If an Auto Refill item is temporarily out of stock you will receive notification. Your order will ship when the item is back in stock and refill shipments will continue at the specified frequency from the date of the most recent shipment.  Walter Drake will notify you via email or letter if an item has been permanently discontinued.

 \- Remember to look for this icon for eligible products   

### About Us

Click on the question below to expand the answer

Today, Walter Drake is a leading direct marketer of affordable kitchenware, household products, problem solvers, personal care items, gardening and outdoor helpers, personalized gifts, calendars and stationery. The extensive line of products offered provides unique problem-solvers and specialized items for all ages to enjoy.

Mr. Walter Drake, a pioneer in direct mail, began operations in 1947 in Colorado Springs with a single novel idea. In his one-room office, he created a character named “Tommy Turtle,” advertised in magazines like House Beautiful and Harper’s Bazaar. Parents all over the country began signing their children up to receive personalized, upbeat pen pal letters and gifts from Tommy.

As America became a more mobile society during the 1950’s and 60’s, correspondence became a very popular pastime, and Mr. Drake gradually added convenience products including stationery and address labels. Staying true to its founder’s roots, Walter Drake soon began offering beautiful, heartfelt Christmas cards.

As the brand evolved, Walter Drake recognized the growing need for unique, affordable problem solvers throughout the home and began expanding its collection. Today, the brand offers hundreds of hard-to-find products designed to make everyday living easier. From beautiful bedding and functional furniture to quality-crafted kitchenware and easy-care table covers, each exclusive problem-solver is designed with customers is mind.

Mr. Drake sought to inspire and delight his customers, a mission which still drives every decision we make. Now nestled on the banks of the Fox River in Oshkosh, Wisconsin, Walter Drake is still providing unique products and unexpected values inspired by the vision of its founder.

We are always looking for new and innovative products to sell via our website and catalog. Please contact us at the following address with any products you wish to submit. Please supply us with a detailed description, product photos or possibly a sample of your product.

Walter Drake  
Attn: Product Ideas  
250 City Center  
Oshkosh, WI 54906  

Please submit all customer service issues by [CLICKING HERE](https://www.wdrake.com/walterdrake/customerservice/contactus.aspx).

Directions to our Executive Offices  
250 City Center  
Oshkosh, WI  
Phone: 920-231-3800

From Highway 41:  
Exit Highway 41 at 9TH AVENUE  
IF NORTHBOUND: Turn RIGHT  
IF SOUTHBOUND: Turn LEFT  
Turn LEFT onto SOUTH MAIN ST  
Turn LEFT onto CEAPE AVE   
Visitor parking is in front of office along river.

Directions to our Distribution Center  
2155 South Oakwood Road  
Oshkosh, WI  
Phone: 920-231-3800

From Highway 41:  
Exit Highway 41 at Highway 44.  
If NORTHBOUND, turn left.  
If SOUTHBOUND, turn right.  
Turn RIGHT on Highway 91.  
Turn RIGHT on OAKWOOD ROAD.  
Walter Drake is on the left before the stop light.

We recently partnered with Impact Radius to manage our affiliate program. Join our affiliate program today and earn cash by promoting our brand and products on your website. When one of your customers visits our site and makes a purchase, we pay you a commission. For more information and to join, please visit the [Impact Radius affiliate website](http://member.impactradius.com/campaign-campaign-info/Walter-Drake.brand?io=EjTZ2s6yzZuBDmcV0SzS7tnsKAQ0WkDpZ1chWyUdygTEkRshiaX82k94SpUPlNTR).

Did you know?

* Walter Drake Company has invested $150,000 in lighting upgrades at the distribution center that has resulted in the annual electricity savings of 1,100,000 kilowatt hours. This is the equivalent of providing electricity to 100 homes or the energy of 1990 barrels of oil. The impact of this project is reducing our carbon footprint by 2,522,920lbs of CO2 annually. [Click here for more detail](https://www.wdrake.com/walterdrake/images/docs/copy%20of%20environmental%20emissions%20equivalents.xls).  
* Walter Drake Company uses corrugate shipping containers made from over 60% post consumer content.  
* Walter Drake Company is committed to recycling. Annually, our distribution center recycles 600 tons of cardboard and 60 tons of office paper.  
* From 2005 to 2007 our use of lighter weight paper has reduced our total wood use by 1,472 tons, or 10,191 trees. The energy saved was 21,806 million BTU’s, enough to power 240 homes each year. Greenhouse gases were reduced the equivalent of 4,364,582 lbs CO2, or the emissions from 396 cars per year. Wastewater was reduced 10,219,474 gallons. [Click here for more details](https://www.wdrake.com/walterdrake/images/docs/paper%20reduction%202005-2007.pdf).  
* The Walter Drake Foundation donates more than $100,000 each year to support charitable, scientific, literary and educational institutions

[Click here to see our entire environmental policy and vision statement](https://www.wdrake.com/link/62bdfece59414ef6b8eb2c55ff47d9ff.aspx).

### Transparency in Supply Chain

Click on the question below to expand the answer

Silver Star Brands strongly opposes slavery and human trafficking, and would never knowingly conduct business with suppliers of retail products who engage in such practices. With each wholesale order, our business partners are required to certify that all applicable laws are followed in regard to slavery and human trafficking. Our supply chain staff ensure the enforcement of this policy with purchase agreements that prominently state this requirement to our vendors.

Our purchase orders include a provision that requires our vendors to agree to comply with all applicable laws regarding slavery and human trafficking. Silver Star Brands requires that no goods be manufactured in whole or in part with prison labor, forced labor, indentured labor, or child labor.
